Arthur Koton

2387 Ocean Avenue, Brooklyn, NY 11229 - 718-501-0669 - arthurkoton@proton.me

LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/arthurkoton/

Github - https://github.com/arthur-code-don

Portfolio Website: arthurcodedon.com

Frontend Developer

I am enthusiastic web developer who has been coding for 2 years, I am an avid student of programming who has gone through a wide variant of course work, 'freeCodeCamp' 'Coursera' And many other resources such as learning from my fellow peers, all that... has molded me into the passion driven programmer I am today. I have experience with HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Python, and I am a lifelong student, always learning new and interesting things. I am passionate about solving problems, helping people, being apart of something great, greater than myself. Making a difference and solving problems that will make the lives of all of us easier are all things that motivate me.

Within my portfolio you will see not only the numerous projects I have worked on, the thought and effort I put in, the passion I have for my craft, the overall love I have for this field, and all that I have learned over the past couple of years even astounds me. I am grateful for making the career change into a Web Developer, I continue to strive, learn, and hope to turn my skills into a full-time Full-Stack Dev role. I have several certificates from my completed coursework, to which I am proud of, I am committed to the realm of programming, and I am eager to bring value to you and our team.

Skills

- ★ Web Development
 - ★ MySQL
 - **★** HTML
 - * CSS
 - **★** JavaScript
 - **★** UX/UI
 - **★** Python
- ★ Git Version Control
- ★ Great communication skills
 - ★ Detail oriented
 - ★ Analytical thinking
 - **★** Trouble shooter
 - **★** Teamwork

Past Professional Summary

Reliable and Enthusiastic IT Professional with over 10 years of experience in working with computers, technology, software, hardware, and helping clients resolve their computer and technical needs, Customer service is key. I possess tier 1-2 troubleshooting skills for a wide variety of problems, When I'm not working, I spend some additional time on the computer taking on various projects. All of which involve increasing my knowledge and helping others where I can. This is something I am most passionate about, "learning", I'm very passionate about "Information Technology" and "Helping others" I am eager to join a phenomenal Organization, I have extensive knowledge of software, hardware, and web applications. I am also proficient in Windows 7-11 / (windows server) active directory, Linux, anything I don't know - I do my research and learn it.

Work Experience

Transportation dispatcher - Customer Service Representative (Centrek Transportation, NYC) October 2022 – March 2023

- Answer inbound calls and coordinate transportation for members, dispatch trips and act as a liaison between Medicare and Medicaid, among many other health insurance channels, and other dispatchers.
- Answering and Solving company and member requests using voice, text, and emails.
- Utilizing the limosys application, among several other company applications.
- Ensuring customer satisfaction is my focus, along with thorough coordination of transport.

IT Technical Support - Help Desk - Remote work from home (Branded book, NYC) August 2016 - July 2021

- Installing and configuring computer hardware, software, systems, networks, printers and scanners
- Monitoring and maintaining computer systems and networks
- Responding in a timely manner to service issues and requests
- Providing technical support across the company (in person, remote, and over the phone)
- Setting up accounts for new users
- Repairing and replacing equipment as necessary
- Testing new technology
- training junior staff members

Misc. Relevant Experience

Ability to work in a Virtual environment (VMS), Operating systems include (Linux – Utilizing CLI (Terminal) Windows 7-11 / Windows Server (Active Directory) – Group Policy, Users and Computer Management, Installing, Updates, Shared folders, Remote Desktop Connections, SSH, VPNS, DNS / DHCP / Static IP / BIOS Configuration / Hardware / Software installation / Troubleshooting (including peripheral devices (printers) / Creating Documentation / Backups – Restores, Encryption, Formats, Installing OS, (Linux, Windows). Repairing/Recovering/Replacing hardware such as hard drives, ram, and software.

Core Qualification

Detail-oriented / Customer service-focused / Meticulous and Organized / Exemplary communication skills / Team Player / Punctual / Dependable / Honest / Attentive to detail / Fast learner / Hard working / Work well with staff and clients / Computer hardware & software technology / Analytical / problem solving skills / DHCP/DNS Ethernet – Wireshark – Packet Tracer - TCP/IP – Firewall / Proficient in Printers, Phones (mobile phones : IOS/Android), Security / Online Support / Software installs / update management / Hardware Configuration / Oracle – Virtual Machines – Servers / Deployments / Active Directory / MSDS knowledge / Windows 7-11 & Windows Server 2012 – 2016 /

Microsoft Office / Linux / UNIX / Mac OS X / Adobe Photoshop / After Effects / SCCM, Spiceworks, PDQ deploy +
Inventory / Salesforce / Ticketing System: Remedy / Jira Service Desk / Types 60+ WPM / html – CSS – JavaScript – C

- VScode – Node.js - MySQL – Chrome Dev tools - Git CLI – GitHub – Repositories / Full stack dev – Docker –

Angular – Maven – Jenkins – Silenium / python / Unity – Unreal Engine / Solidity / NFT creation / Smart Contracts /

Token Creations / experienced in various coding languages.

Education

- DeVry University 2010 2012: Business Administration
- Abraham Lincoln High School / 2003 / High school Equivalency Diploma Brooklyn, New York

<u>Hobbies</u>

- Working on various Projects, NFTs, Solidity Coding, Smart Contract Creation and Deployments, Crypto enthusiast, Unreal Engine, Unity3D, learning game development. My biggest hobby is undoubtably learning new things.
- Spending time with loved ones.

Course & Certification

- Python 3 Course 2022
- Computer Science 2022
- Coding Technology 2022
- Web Development 2022
- Game Design Devlopment 2022
- Artificial Intelligence 2022
- Cyber Security 2022
- System Administration & IT Infrastructure services 2019
- Active Directory User Management -2018
- Office 365 Administrator 2018

REFERENCES ARE AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST